♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
We now return to Hotel TV,
the station that makes you feel
like you're at a hotel
when you're not at a hotel.
Have a romantic drink
by the concourse fountain.
Or you can watch the big game
at Chopper's Bar and Grill,
where they'll be pouring
till 2:00 a.m.
Or maybe you're in the mood
for something
a little more exotic.
Try Jose Gato's
Brazilian Steakhouse.
With rooftop views,
plus a fine selection
of blended rum drinks.
At the end of the night,
you won't want to say,
"Boa noite."
And you won't have to,
'cause Chopper's is open,
where they're pouring
till 2:00 a.m.
Should we go
to Chopper's?
We interrupt this program
to bring you a Chanel 5 News
special report.
Good evening, Quahog.
I'm Tom Tucker.
Tragedy stuck Haiti today
as the island nation was rocked
by a major earthquake,
leaving thousands dead
and injured.
Coming up, local newsman
shows a camera operator
how to center a shot.
There we go.
There, there's Tom.
There's the star.
Oh, my God.
That's terrible about Haiti.
We got to do
something to help.
No, we don't.
Relax.
I'm sure Wyclef Jean
has got it all under control.
I've always talked about
wanting to help in
these situations,
but I never
follow through.
Well, this time, I'm
really gonna do it.
I'm gonna start
a blood drive.
Good for you, Lois.
You'll be a local hero,
like Paul Revere.
The British will
be here soon.
We shall stand our ground
and fight them to the death!
Yes! Yes!
Although...
I mean, one of us
should probably
warn everyone.
You know... that the
British are coming.
I mean, not me.
I mean,
I want to fight.
I mean, oh, shoot...
I've got the horse.
I mean, but if
anyone else wants to go?
I'll go.
No one?
All right.
I'll make sure everyone
remembers your names!
Wow, Lois, you really
got a great turnout
for the blood drive.
Oh, yeah.
The whole thing's going off
without a hitch.
Well, except
for that mosquito
who keeps trying
to sneak in.
Hi. I'm the new nurse.
Get out of here!
This blood's not for you!
Aw...
Oh, look, an empty tire
with some water in it.
All right,
I'm happy again.
I'm gonna go ahead
and thank you
for donating
blood today.
Donating?!
I thought we were
getting paid!
Peter, everyone else here
has donated except you.
That's not true.
That guy over there
didn't donate.
That's still
you, Peter.
Oh. Well, if I got to donate,
he's got to donate, too.
You, get in here!
Sucker!
Son of a bitch!
Lois! Lois!
Mommy!
Stewie,
what's going on?
You should be
asleep by now.
I can't sleep, Brian.
Where's the woman?
I need her to read me
a bedtime story.
Oh, she's busy with
the blood drive.
Maybe I can help.
How about I read you
this book?
It's called
Apathetic George.
"George used to be
a curious monkey,
"but after
a month in captivity,
"all he did
was wait for food.
"The zoo people
wanted him to mate,
"but he lost interest
in that, too.
"20 years
and millions of dollars
in zoo revenue later,
he died."
Okay, I've had enough.
All right, you know what,
I know something that will help
you sleep. Wait here.
Well, I hope so.
Because I've tried everything.
Counting sheep,
thinking sleepy thoughts.
I even hired the Sandman.
Sand and sand and
sand and sand
and sand and sand
and good night!
Okay, I'll give you
a tiny bit of this.
It should help you sleep.
What is it?
It's cough syrup.
It's not really for kids,
but a capful
is pretty harmless.
Mmm.
Oh, so this is what Lil Wayne
keeps almost dying from.
Ah, this is so relaxing.
I could get used to this.
Like the way I got used to
wearing European diapers.
Don't mind me.
I'm just grabbing
a little cheese and vino.
If anybody needs me,
I'll be poolside
next to my weirdly hot
girlfriend with dark teeth.
Well, Lois, I'm
done giving blood.
Just ask this guy.
Is true, Lois.
I sucked him dry.
He gave a blood
donation as well.
Peter, knock it off.
Just give some blood,
get your cookie
and be done with it.
Cookie?
Yes, Peter.
There are cookies
for everyone who donates.
Well, I already ate
two wedding cakes,
but I guess I could
go for a cookie.
All right, I'll do it.
Peter, you're doing
a good thing.
Thanks, Lois, but you got
to promise you'll warn me
before they stick
that needle in me.
Actually, we
just finished.
Wow, that wasn't so bad.
See, Peter? And now
you can have a cookie.
Oh, awesome!
Mmm. Mmm. Oh, my God,
Th-these are delicious.
Lois, you made these?
Yeah, I found one
of my grandmother's old recipes,
so I thought I'd make a special
batch for the blood drive.
Well, I'm glad you did.
These cookies are amazing.
They're even tastier
than Connie Britton's hair.
Mmm. God, your
hair is delicious.
Who are you?
I'm the guy who killed
your bodyguard.
Coming this fall
to every network,
your favorite sitcom lines
preceded by the word "uh."
Uh, knock much?
Uh, that just happened.
Uh, so I guess this
is a thing now?
Uh, yeah, no.
Uh, awkward.
TV, that thing
you used to watch.
Oh, these are incredible.
Hey, you know something?
If we sold these, we could
make a ton of money.
Maybe we should open
our own cookie store.
Are you serious?
Yeah, why not?
I mean, if George Foreman
can make electric grills,
we can do this.
I mean, I've seen that guy
get punched in the face
a thousand times, and now
he's making science stuff.
Who'd think that idiot
would still be walking around
and Muhammad Ali
can't even talk anymore?
You know, having our own store
could be kind of fun.
And you'd really do it with me?
Absolutely.
Oh, Peter, that actually sounds
kind of romantic.
I always wanted you and me
to work on a project together.
Oh, let's do it!
All right! Now, let's
turn up the TV real loud
so the kids can't
hear us having sex.
Aah! Aah!
Sex! Sex!
There's my handsome
business partner.
Now, we can't be late for
our meeting with the bank.
That's so cool you guys
are gonna open a business.
Yeah, well, I got a ton
of business experience.
I mean, I had that job
creating ads
for the North Dakota
board of tourism.
Hi. Do you like South Dakota
but don't want
to see Mount Rushmore?
Come to North Dakota.
It's just a very long drive
from wherever you live.
Best of all,
most of the good license plates
aren't taken yet.
Imagine coming here
and having "Cool Dude"
or "Yay Jews"
or "Boo Jews,"
depending on where you stand
on Jews.
North Dakota.
We're not even the best Dakota.
Stewie,
what are you doing?
Huh? Oh, Brian,
oh, there you are.
I've been... I've been looking
all over the table for you.
You know, I've got to tell
you, this stuff you gave me
was a lifesaver
last night.
I was out
like a light.
And, you know, normally,
I'm up five or six times
to scream and defecate.
But you know what?
I slept straight
through.
Stewie, I told you,
there's alcohol in that.
It's not for kids.
You're not for kids.
Stewie, you're drunk.
Oh, Brian's all serious.
"Oh, I don't... I don't
drink in the morning
because I've got
to land a plane."
All right, come on, I've got
to drive you to daycare.
Okay, okay, it's all right.
C-Calm down, calm down.
Uh, uh, oh. Oh, I think I...
I think I've put my shoes
on the wrong feet.
Is it 9:15 already?
Lois, we got to go!
You know, I've got all
the papers for the loan officer,
but, I got to admit,
I'm a little nervous.
Don't worry, we're gonna
get this loan, no problem.
And if you get nervous,
just do what I always do,
picture your
audience naked.
Good afternoon,
Mr. and Mrs. Griffin.
Aah! Get that enormous
thing out of my face!
I'll be your loan officer,
so why don't you have a seat
and tell me
about your business.
Our business
is cookies.
Now let me ask
you a question.
You ever heard of money?
Yes.
Good, good. We're
on the same page.
Now, sir, let me ask
you something else.
Can you name one successful
company that isn't cookie-based?
Microsoft.
Peter, I'll handle this.
Uh, my husband and I would like
to open a cookie store.
We've done all the research,
and I'm very confident
we can turn a profit.
I've brought some samples
if you'd like to try one.
She said one.
Take one.
Mmm. Well,
these are delicious.
Let me just run this
by my supervisor.
Yes!
Mr. and Mrs. Griffin,
this bank would like
to help you start
your business.
Really?!
Oh, that's fantastic!
And if you have
any other questions,
you can call me
at any time.
Hello?
How far away are the stars?
Brian! Brian!
Hold-hold on one second.
I'll be right with you,
Mr. Duckford.
Brian!
What?
Let's order... I was just
thinking, let's order a kebab.
A what?
A kebab.
But I... but I want it
in this order:
vegetable, meat, meat,
vegetable, meat.
And, uh, Mr. Duckford
would like some quackers.
Can I leave now?
No, no, Bri... No, you can't.
Brian, I need your help.
I've made a series
of small poops in my bath,
and I need you to scoop them out
with this fishnet.
Yeah, I'm not doing that.
You have to.
You're my butler.
I'm not your butler.
I know, but wouldn't
it be great if you were?
It'd be... I'd be so happy.
In fact, the only thing
that would make me happier is...
would... is... would be if this
tub was filled with "yawgurt."
Can you... can you get me
some yawgurt?
Is the yawgurt shop
still open?
Is there... is there some place
to dial up yawgurt?
Stop saying that.
What's the best skin yawgurt?
Who can... who can prepare me
a nice yawgurt treatment?
If you say it like that one
more time, I'm gonna drown you.
Yawgurt. Uh, see?
You're not... you're not
gonna do anything.
Hey, hey, Brian,
am I a good little guy?
This space
will be perfect, Peter.
Yeah, it sure will, Lois.
Now all we got to do
is name the store.
Ooh, ooh, I got it.
Peter's Wife's Cookies.
I love it.
And I love you.
Really?
Yes.
You know, we did so-so
building a family,
but this business--
I think we can really
knock it out of the park.
Oh, we sure can, Lois.
We're gonna be a great team.
Like Moses and his buddy who
liked to collect seashells.
Yay!
I can't believe it, Peter.
Our first day
of business.
All right. Well,
we have got work to do,
so let's roll up our sleeves
and get right to it.
There's a lot to do,
so we can't be afraid
to just roll up our sleeves
and get the job done.
We can't be hands-off managers.
We got to roll up our sleeves
and just dig in.
Peter, your arms
are turning purple.
Purple with success.
That's the color of money.
You got to do the work of two
men and pay yourself for one.
Just roll up those sleeves
and address the task at hand,
whatever it may be, not shying
away from the dirty work,
but just rolling up our sleeves
and having at it.
Success is not given.
It is taken.
It's time to get in the game
and get dirty.
All right, I'm going to lunch.
Uh, yes, I'd like
a chocolate chip cookie.
Elmer!
What, Mom? You promised
I could get a cookie
if I finished
all my surgery.
Did you?
Yeah.
All of it?
Um...
Get back there.
I'm gonna do it.
What does it matter
when I do it?
Lois, Lois, lock the door.
Why?
It's that lady who comes
in, tries a sample,
and then whispers about
how bad she is. Hey.
Oh, my God, you have
chocolate macadamia nut?
Oh, could I just try
a little sample?
Oh, I'm so bad.
Uh, sure.
You gonna buy a
cookie this time?
Oh, I better just
stick with the sample.
I'm so bad.
But at least
I know I'm bad,
so that makes me
a little less bad.
Or worse.
That was the right thing
to do, Peter.
Oh, boy, it's been
really slow.
I mean, if it doesn't
pick up soon,
we're not gonna stay
in business very long.
Don't you worry,
Lois, you keep baking,
I'll drum up some business.
We just got to think
outside the box,
like the makers of
Dreyer's ice cream.
Guys, I've said it before,
and I'll say it again:
When people go to
the supermarket,
they need something
to look at
before they choose
Haagen-Dazs.
Hey, dude, can you pass me
a speck of Spazz?
Sorry, brah,
all out.
You want a cube
of Froosh?
Nah, I'm not into Froosh.
I got a tear
of Laser Dragon.
Can I handle it?
I don't know.
Can you?
Gum! What the hell is going on?!
I don't know
what to do, you guys.
The cookie shop
is tanking.
If it fails,
we're screwed.
My God,
what does it take
to get people
to buy a damn cookie?
Peter, let me
tell you something.
I spend $600 a month
on scented candles
at the farmer's market
just because there's
a hot chick selling them.
So what are you saying?
You just bragging
about candles?
That's a weird thing
to brag about.
No, I'm saying
sex sells.
Trust me,
you get a few hotties
in that cookie shop
of yours,
I bet your sales
will go up.
Giggity.
That was an unearned
giggity, Quagmire.
I said "up."
No?
No.
Well, I'll try
anything, Quagmire,
'cause I actually like
running that cookie shop.
It's way better
than that job I had
telemarketing
to buttholes.
Hello?
Sorry, wrong number.
And how are you today, sir?
Oh, my God.
Customers.
What the hell?
Peter, what did you do?
I saved our business.
And don't worry,
I only hired women
whose names are
cookie-related.
Lois, meet
Cookie, Sugar,
Spice, Cinnamon,
Brown Sugar
and Butter.
Oh, hey,
Butter.
Some guys
like Butter.
Peter, you turned our store
into a strip club.
And I don't like
what this place has become.
You mean hugely
profitable?
We made all that today?
Well, it was
twice as much,
but I had to bail out
Cinnamon's kid.
Thanks, Mr. Peter.
This guy's the best.
Well, I guess business
is better than ever.
That's the spirit, Lois.
Just you watch, we'll
be a bigger success
than Richard Branson.
Hey, where's the business
guy in this boardroom?
It couldn't be that
tan, long-haired guy
with the white linen
pants, could it?
It is!
And now, to my amphibious
sky submarine.
I have way too much money!
Come on, get-get down there,
you old bag.
There we go.
Stewie, what are you doing?
Being awesome.
Whoa, whoa,
wait, wait.
You're in no
condition to drive.
I'm fine to drive.
I'm so fine.
You s...
I can do all the tests.
See?
I can touch my nose.
I can touch my...
♪ Head, shoulder, knees
and toes, knees and toes. ♪
Stop it.
No, you stop it.
You stop it, Brian.
You're interfering
with my professional
business.
Where's the radio?
Oh, my God, are you okay?
No. I don't feel so good.
We should probably
exchange numbers.
Okay. I'm a ten,
you're a four.
This one's our new
chocolate white chocolate,
and for every
dozen we sell,
we donate 50 cents
to Operation Smile.
Yeah, nobody's
listening to you.
They're all watching Sugar
write frosting
swears on her jugs.
She just wrote
"vagina" on her boobs.
That doesn't even
make any sense.
She's doing what?
I told her ten minutes ago
to put another batch
of oatmeal in the oven.
Oh, that dough
is gone, Lois.
I warmed it up
and put it behind
those waist-high
holes in the wall.
Is it spaghetti?
A bowl of grapes?
Ooh, this is the best
haunted house ever.
Peter, this is disgusting.
I know we made a few changes,
but this store should
still be about selling cookies.
Well, you're never gonna
sell any looking like that.
There. Now you're
ready to sell cookies.
You know what?
That's it. I'm done.
I don't know why I ever
let you talk me into this...
this...
whatever this is now.
It's a strip club that
gives away free cookies.
Ugh.
Oh, crap.
I should've known
something was up
when I saw all those
cars out front.
Stewie, why don't you
come and have a seat
with all your friends here?
We have something
to say to you.
I'll go first.
"Stewie, I remember
the day you were born.
"I thought to myself,
here's a kid
"who's got a white,
empty canvas
stretched out
in front of him."
Oh, please.
What... Who...
What is this...
What is this,
the circle
of perfect people?
Who are you
to judge me?
Mis-Mister...
Mister Giraffe,
who lets l-little boys
grind on his rump.
Mr. Octopus, who lets
little boys grind on his rump.
Every one of you
has your own problems.
Yeah, but you're
the only one who almost
killed a kid yesterday.
Yeah, well, that's, d...
That's because that...
'Cause, because that
kid... That's because...
because that... 'ca...
because that kid...
that kid...
I know.
Oh, Brian.
Who am I?
I don't have a cough,
and my sinuses
are remarkably
wide open.
But I have a problem.
Good. Admitting it
is the first step.
But don't worry,
I'll get you through it.
Thank you, Brian.
You're welcome, Stewie.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go to Chris's room.
We're doing
a masturbation intervention.
I got a bunch of his friends
sitting in a circle in there...
Oh, dear God.
Oh. Hey.
Lois, before you
say anything,
there's something
important I want to tell you.
After you left, I ate
cookie dough off the stomach
of a 20-year-old,
and then I vomited
and all the girls
laughed at me,
and then it came out that they
all think I'm fat and old.
Is that it?
I guess what I'm trying
to say is...
I was wrong to choose
sexiness over my wife.
Peter, what are you doing?
What-what was that?
Oh, back at the store,
I, uh, tucked my boner
into the waistband of my pants
and now it's sitting weird.
That's your apology?
Well, that and this.
Oh, Peter, did...
did you bake this?
Yeah. I love you, Lois.
I really liked
having a store with you,
and I'm...
I'm sorry I messed it up.
I was only trying to help.
I know, Peter.
So you want
to split this with me?
Uh, I wouldn't.
Butter helped me with it,
and she has
chlamydia fingers.
Well, it was fun
having our own store.
But from now on,
my cookies
are only
for these customers.
Oh, Mom.
So, Mom, what are you
gonna do with the shop?
Well, I talked
to the bank,
and they agreed
to take it back.
Me love Cookie. Om, nom, nom,
nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom...
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru